Last time Gordon Ramsey makes a spy. Rice so good.
Uncle Roger called him Uncle Gordon. This time
he begged me. King Ramen. Can he keep his uncle title,
or is he going to lose it? Let's see. Let's see.
Halloween and nephew new neon sign. Uncle Roger
Rice cooker. What do you think? What you think? Leave comment.
Let Uncle Roger know what you think of my neon light underneath
the neon light.
Wait, before we even start, why Gordon looks so shiny.
What is this, medium to saw bullshit?
Right? Come on. Let's be honest, ramen, is that comfort food that we all love,
especially on a cold day? But today, trust me, I'm going to show you how
to elevate that notoriously cheap dish into something delicious. And guess
what? Give me a V. That's right. Vegetarian.
Right. What making vegetarian
food? Cotton. I thought you hate vegetarian. I'm allergic
to vegetarians. I come out in a rash. Why you make vegetarian
food now? Garden. Why you bow down to those people? What's the
point of having all those knives back there if you're vegetarian?
Were you gonna use the clever for Pok Choy? Um, and guess what?
Give me a V. But give me a we is actually good pickup
line. He's a nephew. Go to bar, find woman you like, and tell
her to give you a wee. Sorry, children. Right.
Come in, Oscar. Let me show you the ingredients. Egg noodles.
Egg noodle, uncle Gordon already made mistake.
Egg noodle. Raw noodles. Ramen should use wheat alkaline noodles.
That's not starting well. Three and a half minutes.
Beautiful. Seaweed scallion. Seaweed good scallion tofu correct.
Ginger. Good cauliflower. These are the secret ingredients.
These are cauliflower, uh, dried shiitake mushrooms. They're going to go in
good. And they're going to rehydrate. Right. Let's have ten minutes
on the clock. Wait. Ramen take at least 10 hours.
He's making in ten minutes. I don't think this
is going to go well. Keep watching. See if Uncle Roger correct. Get them
with a spoon and drop them into that water. Okay? Please tell me
six minutes. Six minutes. Correct. Bring it up to the boil.
Boil them gently, and I want to ball that. Put a little bit of sort
of yolky bit in the middle. Good. Software immediately.
Okay. In mushroom in water. Sort of go
up a level. Okay. I hope he making Tara
and not just working everything in pan. Turn, uh,
the gas up. Okay. And now we're going to start creating
that base. First off,
a tablespoon of Meat's paste. No,
don't put miso paste in your boiling water. It's going
to kill the miso. You want to make miso? Make misotari
separately. Hi. This, uh, is the same mistake Nigel I lost
on making her ramen. Gordon, you make
me so sad. Okay, and give that a really good mix.
Now, those mushrooms are doubling in size. Doubling in size.
Just like Aunty Herald after our marriage. And the exciting thing now
is that it starts and give flavor. That water. Wait,
just one tablespoon miso in that big pot water.
What's the point? Not going to taste like anything.
This just Husky hit of miso. That not enough. A Husky
hit of miso from there.
Tablespoon of soy. Now you're just working
random shit in boiling water. Touch a mirror
because it gives it a little bit of lift and a bit of a bite.
One of my favorites, takarashi spice. Beautiful Japanese pepper in
lightly seasoning with the chili flakes. White chili
flakes and Takarushi pepper. Same thing. You're wasting money
and wasting time. Get your egg noodles in
and then. No, don't put your
egg noodle wrong. Noodle. First of
all. And don't put your noodle in the broth.
You should Cook separately. The broth needs time to extract
flavor out of ingredients. You put no doubt in broth for that long,
it's going to be Socky and dead in the anxiety.
Caught, uh uh, on every step. Wrong so far.
What happening? What's happening? The gas.
Okay, that's right. Turn off the gas.
Now give that a good mix. Taste that broth
white taste for what? Shit in water for two
minutes. Where could taste? You're just tasting soy sauce and water.
Two minutes. Not long enough for anything. Trust me. Uncle Roger know.
Delicious. Plus more salt. Okay, for me. And then
a little bit of salt and look, the seaweed.
Seaweed. Now I just cut off. No.
What's, uh, he doing? What's he doing? Oh my God.
Seaweed into boiling water. What are you doing?
Garden seaweed broth. I'm just
going to disintegrate into the water. You killing
me, Gordon. And you're killing the seaweed. Uncle Roger have to put my
leg down from chair already. Gordon,
you fucked up. See, we supposed to go in ramen last thing
right before you eat. Like go watch Uncle Roger make ramen
with Joe. See how it done. Nice. Long. Sort of almost strip.
Like Juliet. No. Uh, every minute this broth is
getting better, tastier and deeper.
It's getting wrong. Good. Is that what it gets? Vegetables and
then just taste again. Good.
Now it's nearly there. Nearly. Uh, where? Hell, that where
tofu. Just literally
tofu. Okay, because vegetarian beautiful strands.
Not my first choice, but okay, I just place that on top.
Wait. Tofu. Straight into what in
vegetarian ramen tofu replace the pork belly. So you
need to marinate the tofu first. Don't just serve raw
tofu. It just tastes like bean marinade.
Oscar, please come down. Have a quick look at
the smorgasbord of delicious ingredients that look just like miso
soup. Where co ramen don't look like ramen at all. If your
ramen look like miso soup, you fucked up delicious ingredients,
man. That's good. That's so good, man. That's good. He kept tasting
and he keep lying. Take your cephal oil and
just sesame oil. I think,
uh, that's going to be the only aroma oil he used.
Sure. The gas is off. I want to touch more spice
in there for me. Just a touch. Let it simmer the gap.
This ramen is not jazz. You don't just implement
passes off. Okay? Eggs are boiling time,
please. Right. Three minutes down. Cauliflower. Cauliflower.
Now, this gives a bit of texture for ramen.
It's a great way, I guess, for vegetarian ramen flower.
Okay, these bits here, just cut around
there. Slice those bits nice and thin. And these stalks
are so delicious. Stock. Delicious. Stock is
worst part of vegetable. Um, Uncle Roger don't, um, like vegetable.
Vegetables tastes like sad. But if Uncle Roger has to eat vegetable,
I eat the leaf, because stock tastes as shit. As leaf,
but harder to chew. Stock is the same shit food, but more
effort. Who want that? Okay. Like the storks on a
broccoli. Beautiful ramen. And put
those stalks in there. Uh, take your cauliflower.
He's still going on about cauliflower.
Lightly season it does that with, uh, some rice flour.
Crunch cauliflower. So when we frock on some chili
in there. So I got some heat. Okay? And then look a
nice little shallow, fly hot pan. Uh, get the
oil in. Nice, crispy texture that sits
on top of those noodles.
Is this ramen weejo, or is this cauliflower?
With sight of chicken noodleujo. He spent 30 seconds making
ramen broth and 3 hours making cauliflower.
All this, uh, time. Meanwhile, the noodle in that pot just drowning
again. I love frying a nonstick
pan because I get that texture. I really get it nice and soft. Nonstick.
You just say nonstick, and then you use metal spoon.
Cannot use metal spoon in nonstick garden.
Uh, why like this? Uh,
today? What's wrong with you? It looked like you came out
about getting your shirt to match the cabinet. They're making good food,
but look. Look at the color of that cauliflower.
Beautiful. Now it's going Golden Brown. Can we go back
to ramen now, please? I want a little slice of
kitchen towel. Get that ready. Uh,
colander and cauliflower together this week. Have all of Uncle
Roger nightmare. I think it's really nice and crispy.
I've got a chili in there as well.
My mom going to go beat you up. Gordon, scrape, uh, scrape.
Scrape with metal spoon. Some wonderful spring
onion. Okay, spring onion. Good. Finally, we done with cauliflower
on the bias, so I go sideway this time.
Sideway. Uncle Roger likes sideways also,
and the sort of white parts. Again, I'm just going to sprinkle in.
Oh, you sprinkle into broth. Spring onion
and ramen broth. Okay, but you're not going to have enough time to
get the flavor out. Ten minutes. One more final
taste. Look at it in there.
Oscar, come in, come in. Pan down. Don't tell
Oscar to pan down. Uncle Roger want you to
put your pan down. Stop cooking.
That is so delicious. Now, eggs. Take them
out. I always like to sort of put them into cold waterfall. Ok,
correct. Egg and ice bath. Correct. Right. Time to
serve. Get your, uh, bowl. This is a very generous sort of family
style dish. Family style. Um, high. But they
eat ramen family style. Wrong bowl.
Okay. Big, deep, beautiful dish
now. Oh, look at it. Oh, my God.
The flavor don't look good.
That ramen looks so dead and lifeless.
90 seconds where I forget this.
Look. It's so weird serving in this la Crusi
sauce panhai. Gordon, just buy
ramen bowl. You cannot afford ramen bowl, is it? Your daughter on Strictly
Come Dancing? Ask her to lend you some money. Buy some ramen Bowl
Tilly, help your old guy out. Go pick up ginger mascallions,
spring onions, and then look this beautiful,
nice, crispy cauliflower on top.
I think this Witcher Gordon, sponsored by cauliflower company.
He spent so much time talking about it. Now with the egg tap, tap,
tap, pull. And then just put in your top of your hand.
Don't blow. You're giving everybody a cold
with don't blow egg. And that
from there. Literally should come off super quick.
Okay, the Ed peeling quite popular. May I give you that runny
yoke and then look. Yoke. Correct. It looked good,
but you need to marinate your egg. Gordon, look at this egg.
It's, uh, whiter than Jamie Oliver. Who wants to eat just from
there? Just literally snip snip.
That is not fresh. Cilantro. Coriander. No coriander
on ramen.
Just because a dish Asian doesn't mean you can just put coriander
on it. Some ramen. Chefs put coriander or cilantro in ramen,
but not like that. It doesn't matter what country you're in. It's all delicious.
And there we are.
What's this? Uncle Roger can't watch anymore. The broth
all wrong. No Tari, barely any aroma oil.
Wrong type of noodle. I know this, uh,
is supposed to be quick. Ten minute ramen. But if you want ramen in ten
minutes, just make instant ramen even that better than this.
Or go to ramen restaurant. Get ramen in ten minutes. Easy.
Gordon, your egg spirit rice so good. Why are ramen so bad?
Uncle Roger cannot call you Uncle Gordon anymore. I need to
take back that title. Gordon, you're supposed to be one of the good ones.
Why you join dark site to
all of you. Thank you for watching Ramsay Intent. If I went too quick.
Oh, he changed shirt. Slow it down. Now don't
forget to pick up Ramsey. Uh, Intent cookbook inspired. Buy this. He got cookbook.
Trust me. You want to come out of much better chef. It's going to teach
all wrong recipes. Is it? Why are you going to use that cleaner
for Bok Choy?
Uncle, you have to change color. I too upset.
Good. Now it's nearly there. Nearly where?
Hell. That way.
By the way, Uncle Roger noticed what is white people
obsession with making food fast? Like this one?
Ramen in ten minutes. Or Jamie olive oil. Cookbook, like, five ingredients.
Just make it properly? Teaching cooking in Asia,
uncle Roger never see anyone go oh I teach you how to make laksa
in nine in it. No it's not going to be good.